globallysearch.com 2019-08-13

# Website Privacy Policy

## _Last Revised: June 8, 2017_

globallysearch Ltd. ( **“globallysearch“** , **“Company” “we”** or **“us“** ) respects the privacy of the users of its website at the address [globallysearch.com](http://globallysearch.com/) (the **“Site“** ) ( **“User”** or **“you”** ) and is committed to protect the personal information that its Users share with it. We believe that you have a right to know our practices regarding the information we may collect and use when you use our Site. 

Capitalized terms which are not defined herein, shall have the meaning ascribed to them in our Terms of Use at [globallysearch.com/terms.php](http://globallysearch.com/terms.php) ( **“Terms”** ), which this Privacy Policy is incorporated thereto by reference. 

### Your Consent (PLEASE READ CAREFULLY!)

BY ACCESSING THE SITE AND/OR USING THE SITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY (THE **“PRIVACY POLICY“** ), INCLUDING TO THE COLLECTION AND PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS DEFINED BELOW). IF YOU DISAGREE TO ANY TERM PROVIDED HEREIN, YOU MAY NOT USE THE SITE. 

### Which information we may collect on our Users?

We may collect two types of data and information from our Users: 

  * The first type of information is non-identifiable and anonymous information ( **“Non-personal Information”** ). **We are not aware of the identity of the User from which we have collected the Non-personal Information.** Non-Personal Information is any unconcealed information which is available to us while Users are using the Site. Non-personal Information which is being gathered consists of technical information and behavioral information, and may contain, among other things, the activity of the User on the Site, type of operation system, User’s ‘clickstream’ on the Site, browser and keyboard language, etc. 
  * The second type of information is individually identifiable information ( **“Personal Information”). This information may identify an individual or may be of a private and/or sensitive nature**. 

Users of the Site automatically provide their IP address mainly for enhancing the User’s experience and for geolocation and security purposes as further detailed below. In addition, Personal Information which is being gathered consists of any personal details provided consciously and voluntarily by the User. The Personal Information is collected from the details the Users provide within the contact form (“Contact Form”) within our Site which includes their full name, phone number, e-mail address, company name and which of our departments such User is interested in. 

For avoidance of doubt, any Non-Personal Information connected or linked to any Personal Information shall be deemed as Personal Information as long as such connection or linkage exists. 

**We do not collect any Personal Information from you or related to you without your approval, which is obtained, inter alia, through your active acceptance to the Terms and the Privacy Policy.**

### How Do We Collect Information on Our Users?

There are two main methods we use: 

  * **We collect information through your use of the Site.** In other words, when you are using the Site we are aware of it and may gather, collect and record the information relating to such usage, either independently or through the help of third-party services as detailed below. 
  * **We collect information which you provide us voluntarily.|** For example, we collect Personal information which you voluntarily provide through the Site including without limitation via the Contact Form. We store the Personal Information either independently or through the help of our authorized third-party service providers as detailed below. 

### What are the Purposes of the Collection of Information?

Non-personal Information is collected in order to: 

  * Use it for statistical and research purposes and for customization and improvement of our Site’s interface. 
  * Personal Information is collected in order to: 
  * Provide users with the ability to use our Site. 
  * Be able to contact Users who requested to be contacted via our Contact Form. 
  * Determine general geolocation information (i.e., country) from which the User’s computer is connected to the Internet in order for us to know the general location of our Site’s Users as well as in order to safeguard our Site. 

### Sharing Information with Third Parties

globallysearch will not share any Personal Information it collects with any third party. Notwithstanding, globallysearch may disclose Personal Information in the following cases: (a) to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, subpoena or governmental request; (b) to enforce this Privacy Policy and/or the Terms, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (c) to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (d) respond to claims that any content available on the Site violates the rights of third-parties; (f) to respond to claims that contact information (e.g. name, e-mail address, etc.) of a third-party has been posted or transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment; (g) to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of globallysearch, its Users, or the general public; (h) when globallysearch is undergoing any change in control, including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of its assets; or (i) to collect, hold and/or manage your Personal Information through globallysearch’s authorized third party service providers, as reasonable for business purposes, which may be located in a country that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction; (j) pursuant to your explicit approval prior to the disclosure; or (k) cooperate with third parties for the purpose of enhancing the User’s experience. For avoidance of doubt, globallysearch may transfer and disclose Non-personal Information to third parties at its own discretion. 

### Minors

To use of Site, you must be over the age of thirteen (13). Therefore, globallysearch does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of thirteen (13) and does not wish to do so. We reserve the right to request proof of age at any stage so that we can verify that minors under the age of thirteen (13) are not using the Site. 

### Security

We take a great care in implementing and maintaining the security of our Site and its User’s Personal Information. globallysearch employs industry standard procedures and policies to ensure the safety of its Users’ Personal Information, and prevent unauthorized use of any such information. However, we do not guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur. 

### Third Party Software/Service

While using the Site we may be using third party software and/or service, in order to collect and/or process the information detailed herein. Such software including without limitation, and Amazon cloud services which privacy policy can be found at: <http://aws.amazon.com/privacy/>. 

### Third Party Sites

While using the Site you may encounter links to third party websites. Please be advised that such third party websites are independent sites, and we assume no responsibility or liability whatsoever with regard to privacy matters or any other legal matter with respect to such sites. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policies and the terms of use or service of such websites. 

### Cookies

When you access or use the Site, the Company may use industry-wide technologies such as “cookies” (or similar technologies), which store certain information on your computer and which will allow us to enable automatic activation of certain features, and make your service experience much more convenient and effortless. The cookies used by the Site are created per session, does not include any information about you, other than your session key and are removed as your session ends. It is easy to prohibit certain cookies. Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer’s hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, if you block or erase cookies your online experience may be limited. 

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

The terms of this Privacy Policy will govern the use of the Site and any information collected therein. globallysearch reserves the right to change this policy at any time, so please re-visit this page frequently. We will provide notice of substantial changes of this policy on the homepage of the Site and/or we will send you an e-mail regarding such changes to the e-mail address that you may have provided us with. Such substantial changes will take effect seven (7) days after such notice was provided on our Site or sent by email. Otherwise, all other changes to this Privacy Policy are effective as of the stated “Last Revised” date and your continued use of the Site after the Last Revised date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.
